Guide to the Vassar College Student Materials Collection, 1859-2025 (bulk 1867-1950)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES IX. SCRAPBOOKS (Memory Books), 1871-1963; [362 volumes]
  - VC 1883 — Jones, Martha (Boyd), 1879-1883 (Scrapbook 47)
  - VC Ex 1883 — Poucher, Emily (Rollinson), 1878-1939 (Scrapbook 48)
  - VC 1883 — Tucker, Martha (Sharpe), 1878-1888 (Scrapbook 217 (Oversize))
  - VC 1884 — Class scrapbook [Missing as of November 2022] (Scrapbook 49)
  - VC 1884 — Crandall, Catharine (Patterson), 1880-1884 (Scrapbook 50)
  - VC 1884 — Crandall, Catharine (Patterson), 1883-1891 (Scrapbook 218 (Oversize))
  - VC 1884 — Morrill, Lula M., 1880-1884 (Scrapbook 51)
  - VC 1884 — Morrill, Lula M., 1880-1884 (Scrapbook 52)
  - VC 1884 — Stanton, H. Louise (Cornwell), 1879-1884 (Scrapbook 53)
  - VC 1884 — Townsend, Emily A. [Missing as of November 2022], undated (Scrapbook 54)
  - VC 1884-1885 [Special] — Baker, Mary Chase (Donahue), 1882-1885 (Scrapbook 55)
  - VC 1884-1885 [Special] — Kimball, Emma (Palmer) (Scrapbook 213 (Oversize))
  - VC 1885 — Charlton, Edith (Lowry), 1880-1885 (Scrapbook 349 (Oversize))
  - VC 1885 — Davis, Lucy, 1881-1885 (Scrapbook 57)
  - VC 1885 — Durfee, Harriet A., 1881-1885 (Scrapbook 220 (Oversize))
  - VC 1885 — Hening, Sarah C., 1881-1884 (Scrapbook 58)
  - VC 1885 — Hening, Sarah C., 1883-1885 (Scrapbook 330 (Oversize))
  - VC 1885 — Leonard, Ella S., 1881-1883 (Scrapbook 59)
  - VC 1885 — Leonard, Ella S., 1883-1885 (Scrapbook 60)
  - VC 1885 — Shaw, Mary E. (Ewing), 1881-1889 (Scrapbook 219 (Oversize))
  - VC 1886 — Botsford, Helen C., 1883-1886 (Scrapbook 301 (Oversize))
  - VC 1886 — Laporte, Helen (Reed), 1885-1889 (Scrapbook 61)
  - VC 1886 — Laporte, Helen (Reed), 1885-1889 (Scrapbook 62)
  - VC 1886 — Newell, Louise L., 1882-1886 (Scrapbook 63)
  - VC 1886 — Overman, Caroline (Lingle), 1881-1886 (Scrapbook 64)
  - VC 1888 — Briggs, Grace (Rideout), 1882-1890 (Scrapbook 351 (Oversize))
  - VC 1888 — Hatcher, Orie Latham, 1886-1889 (Scrapbook 65)
  - VC 1888 — Nicholson, Eugenie (Kountze), 1884-1888 (Scrapbook 352 (Oversize))
  - VC 1888 — Strong, Eliza (McCreery), 1884-1888 (Scrapbook 350 (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1888 — Reynolds, Martha (Millard), 1885-1898 (Scrapbook 66)
  - VC 1888-1890 [Special, Art]— Hooker, Margaret H. (Scrapbook 67)
  - VC 1889 — Catterall, Helen (Tunnicliff), 1884-1888 (Scrapbook 68)
  - VC 1889 — Catterall, Helen (Tunnicliff), 1888-1891 (Scrapbook 69)
  - VC 1889 — Judy, Elizabeth (Griggs), 1885-1889 (Scrapbook 234 (Oversize))
  - VC 1890 — Lockwood, Mary (Lamson), 1888-1895 (Scrapbook 357 (Oversize))
  - VC 1891 — Clark, Frances (Underhill), 1886-1891 (Scrapbook 270 (Oversize))
  - VC 1891 — Shelden, Helen G., 1885-1887 (Scrapbook 70)
  - VC 1891 — Taylor, Dora N., 1886-1889 (Scrapbook 71)
  - VC 1891 — Taylor, Dora N., 1889-1891 (Scrapbook 72)
  - VC 1892 — Martin, Alice (Robbins), 1888-1894 (Scrapbook 232 (Oversize))
  - VC 1892 — Miller, Lucia (Wood), 1888-1921 (Scrapbook 73)
  - VC 1892 — Morrill, Hester B., 1888-1890 (Scrapbook 74)
  - VC 1892 — Toye, Rebecca (Brush), 1888-1895 (Scrapbook 348 (Oversize))
  - VC 1893 — Clark, Mary Vida, 1888-1898 (Scrapbook 226 (Oversize))
  - VC 1893 — Clark, Mary Vida, 1889-1893 (Scrapbook 227 (Oversize))
  - VC 1893 — Cobb, Eliza P., 1889-1934 (Scrapbook 75)
  - VC Ex 1893 — Loyd, Alberta, 1889-1891 (Scrapbook 76)
  - VC 1893 — Tennant, Anne (Van Syckel), undated (Scrapbook 77)
  - VC 1894 — Bernd, Florence, 1890-1895 (Scrapbook 78)
  - VC 1894 — Elsworth, Ethel Hinton, 1890-1897 (Scrapbook 223 (Oversize))
  - VC 1894 — Humpstone, Mabel (Hastings), 1890-1892 (Scrapbook 79)
  - VC 1894 — May, Louisa Surre, 1891-1914 (Scrapbook 80)
  - VC 1894 — Moore, Ethel, 1890-1892 (Scrapbook 81)
  - VC 1895 — Hill, Clara M., undated (Scrapbook 225 (Oversize))
  - VC 1895 — Updegraff, Elizabeth, 1891-1897 (Scrapbook 233 (Oversize))
  - VC 1895-1896 [Special] — Hughes, Sarah Elizabeth (Scrapbook 82)
  - VC 1896 — Beach, Laura J., 1891-1900 (Scrapbook 83)
  - VC 1896 — Burr, Lula Phinney, 1892-1896 (Scrapbook 84)
  - VC 1896 — Green, Lilian (Bayliss), 1894-1896 (Scrapbook 85)
  - VC 1896 — Howland, Alice M., 1892-1896 (Scrapbook 86)
  - VC 1896 — Kinkead, Cornelia D., 1892-1915 (Scrapbook 354 (Oversize))
  - VC 1896 — Reynolds, Kate B., 1892-1898 (Scrapbook 87)
  - VC 1896 — Russell, Lucile (Cross) [contains VC 1924 Jeanne (Russell) Janish in the same volume], 1887-1938 (Scrapbook 250 (Oversize))
  - VC 1896 — Sheppard, Louise P., 1892-1894 (Scrapbook 88)
  - VC 1896 — Sheppard, Louise P., 1894-1897 (Scrapbook 89)
  - VC 1896 — Sheppard, Louise P., 1900-1911 (Scrapbook 90)
  - VC 1896 — Sheppard, Louise P., 1920-1950 (Scrapbook 91)
  - VC 1896 — Sheppard, Louise P., 1912-1919 (Scrapbook 92)
  - VC 1896 — Smith, Gertrude Lydia (Chesley), undated (Scrapbook 93)
  - VC 1896 — Stamford, Helen, 1890-1904 (Scrapbook 94)
  - VC 1896 — Wing, Lucy Madeira, 1892-1915 (Scrapbook 95)
  - VC 1897 — Bishop, Elizabeth L., 1894-1896 (Scrapbook 96)
  - VC 1897 — Bishop, Helen L., 1892-1893 (Scrapbook 97)
  - VC Ex 1897 — Capwell, Abbey, 1893-1895 (Scrapbook 98)
  - VC Ex 1897 — Howe, Grace (Hartley), 1893-1895 (Scrapbook 99)
  - VC 1897 — Mansfield, Adelaide (Claflin), 1893-1897 (Scrapbook 100)
  - VC 1897 — Post, Anna W., 1893-1915 (Scrapbook 101)
  - VC 1897 — Schauffler, Rachel Capen, 1893-1897 (Scrapbook 102)
  - VC 1897 — Smith, Gertrude, 1893-1897 (Scrapbook 103)
  - VC 1897 — Stribling, Mary (Merrill), 1892-1896 (Scrapbook 104)
  - VC 1897 — Taylor, Louise Clinton [Missing as of August 2010], undated (Scrapbook 105)
  - VC 1897 — Thwing, Mary (Dunning), 1893-1897 (Scrapbook 106)
  - VC 1897— Chesley, Mabel L. [Missing as of November 2022], 1893-1897 (Scrapbook 107)
  - VC Ex 1898 — Aaron, Stella (Hamburger), 1895-1898 (Scrapbook 108)
  - VC 1898 — Humphrey, Eleanor (Belknap), 1892-1896 (Scrapbook 109)
  - VC 1898 — Seymour, Bina, 1891-1898 (Scrapbook 110)
  - VC 1898 — Vassar, Elizabeth Forbes, 1895-1897 (Scrapbook 229 (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — Bindelman, Elinor, 1895-1899 (Scrapbook 347 (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — James, Jean E., 1898-1899 (Scrapbook 111)
  - VC 1899 — James, Jean E., 1894-1898 (Scrapbook 346 (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — Morris, Emma (Garrett), 1895-1896 (Scrapbook 353 (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — Rabell, Alice (Taggart), 1889-1898 (Scrapbook 245.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — Rabell, Alice (Taggart), 1897-1898 (Scrapbook 245.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1899 — Waterman, Helen (Blumenthal), 1895-1901 (Scrapbook 112)
  - VC 1900 — Ehrich, Adelaide (Wallach), 1896-1902 (Scrapbook 355 (Oversize))
  - VC 1900 — Merrill, Isabel (Trowbridge), 1862-1899 (Scrapbook 113)
  - VC 1900 — Merrill, Isabel (Trowbridge), 1900-1901 (Scrapbook 114)
  - VC 1900 — Pierce, Theresa, 1896-1897 (Scrapbook 115)
  - VC 1900 — Tarbox, Julia B., 1896-1897 (Scrapbook 116)
  - VC 1901 — Coffin, Gertrude (Burleigh), 1896-1901 (Scrapbook 117)
  - VC 1901 — Dickson, Eleanor (Gregg), 1897-1901 (Scrapbook 118)
  - VC 1901 — Swartz, Helen M., 1897-1902 (Scrapbook 356 (Oversize))
  - VC 1901 — Thornton, Ruth (Moser), 1897-1908 (Scrapbook 249 (Oversize))
  - VC 1902 — Lavertu, Elsa (White), 1898-1902 (Scrapbook 119)
  - VC Ex 1902 — McCurdy, Florence, 1898-1902 (Scrapbook 120)
  - VC 1903 — Ambler, Alice May, 1899-1903 (Scrapbook 121)
  - VC 1903 — Barratt, Amelia S., 1899-1921 (Scrapbook 122)
  - VC 1903 — Elting, Martha, undated (Scrapbook 123)
  - VC 1903 — Freeman, Sara, undated (Scrapbook 237 (Oversize))
  - VC 1903 — King, Gertrude Besse, undated (Scrapbook 266 (Oversize))
  - VC 1904 — Belding, Isabel (Wheeler), 1900-1904 (Scrapbook 124)
  - VC 1904 — Crippen, Ruth H., 1900-1902 (Scrapbook 125)
  - VC 1904 — Crippen, Ruth H., 1902-1904 (Scrapbook 126)
  - VC 1904 — Devine, Florence (Pelton), 1900-1902 (Scrapbook 127)
  - VC 1904 — Holbrook, Helen S., 1900-1904 (Scrapbook 251 (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1904 — Kautz, Dorothy L., 1899-1901 (Scrapbook 128)
  - VC 1904 — Osborne, Minette (Hegeman), 1900-1921 (Scrapbook 242 (Oversize))
  - VC 1904 — Rich, Anna L., 1900-1906 (Scrapbook 283.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1904 — Stanton, Laura, 1900-1904 (Scrapbook 289 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Barden, Bertha R., 1901-1905 (Scrapbook 129)
  - VC 1905 — Grove, Elsa (Butler), 1902-1905 (Scrapbook 263 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Guthrie, Claire (Reiley), 1903-1905 (Scrapbook 267 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Jones, Olga (Hasbrouck), 1901-1905 (Scrapbook 211 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Keeney, Ruth M. [75th Anniversary], 1940 (Scrapbook 130)
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, 1901-1905 (Scrapbook 258 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen, 1902-1971 (Scrapbook 259 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen — commencement and celebration of retirement of H. Kenyon from Board of Trustees, 1939 (Scrapbook 260 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Kenyon, Helen — Dedication of Kenyon Hall, 1934 (Scrapbook 261 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Lane, Hilda (Swift), 1894-1920 (Scrapbook 131)
  - VC 1905 — Martin, Iva (Owen), 1905-1915 (Scrapbook 132)
  - VC 1905 — McClure, Grace (Sample), 1901-1903 (Scrapbook 264 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — McClure, Grace (Sample), 1901-1905 (Scrapbook 265 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 — Meserve, Alice W., 1897-1905; [1 volume, 1 box of separated material] (Scrapbook 133)
  - VC 1905 — Raynor, Charlotte, undated (Scrapbook 135)
  - VC 1905 — Ross, Caroline (Barnes), 1901-1905 (Scrapbook 136)
  - VC 1905 — Tolson, Stella (Watson), 1901-1903 (Scrapbook 239 (Oversize))
  - VC 1905 —Ferguson, Bertha (Street), undated (Scrapbook 137)
  - VC 1906 — Baker, Alice (Holt) (Scrapbook 138)
  - VC 1906 — Baker, Alice (Holt) (Scrapbook 139)
  - VC 1906 — Hall, Edith Grace, 1902-1906 (Scrapbook 247 (Oversize))
  - VC 1906 — Kosmopoulos, [Alice] Leslie (Walker), 1902-1908 (Scrapbook 341 (Oversize))
  - VC 1906 — Little, Lida A., 1902-1903 (Scrapbook 140)
  - VC 1906 — Little, Lida A., 1903-1906 (Scrapbook 269 (Oversize))
  - VC 1906 — Marrett, Grace E., 1902-1906 (Scrapbook 271 (Oversize))
  - VC 1906 — Morse, Marie L. T., 1904-1906 (Scrapbook 141)
  - VC 1906 — Smith, Sidney (Lewis), 1902-1916 (Scrapbook 142)
  - VC 1906 — Stanley, Helen H. (Talcott), undated (Scrapbook 344 (Oversize))
  - VC 1906 — Yerdon, Marion Lucile, 1902-1916 (Scrapbook 274 (Oversize))
  - VC 1907 — Booth, Ruth (Hoag), 1903-1907 (Scrapbook 143)
  - VC 1907 — Jones, Helen (Stone), 1903-1905 (Scrapbook 144)
  - VC 1907 — Jones, Louisa (Brooke), 1904-1909 (Scrapbook 145)
  - VC 1907 — Jones, Louisa (Brooke), 1904-1909 (Scrapbook 146)
  - VC 1907 — Sague, Mary (Landon), 1903-1905 (Scrapbook 147)
  - VC 1907 — Sague, Mary (Landon), 1905-1907 (Scrapbook 148)
  - VC 1907 — Sessions, Mertice, 1903-1906 (Scrapbook 149)
  - VC 1907 — Torrance, Jane, circa 1903-1907 (Scrapbook 150)
  - VC 1907 — Wilson, Mary Constance, 1903-1907 (Scrapbook 358 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Blake, Dorothy (Signor), 1903-1908 (Scrapbook 284 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Churchill, Ruth (Hornblower), 1904-1908 (Scrapbook 285 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Clark, Bertha E., 1904-1907 (Scrapbook 246 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Cox, Anna (Sellers), 1904-1910 (Scrapbook 151)
  - VC 1908 — Griggs, Mary A., 1904-1908 (Scrapbook 152)
  - VC 1908 — Griggs, Mary A., 1904-1907 (Scrapbook 329 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Hequembourg, Hilda M., 1900-1904 (Scrapbook 279 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Phipard, L. Elisabeth, circa 1900-1908; [1 volume, 1 box of separated material] (Scrapbook 153)
  - VC 1908 — Robinson, Gertrude (Bullard), 1903-1907 (Scrapbook 134)
  - VC 1908 — Schermerhorn, Helen I., 1904-1906 (Scrapbook 280.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Schermerhorn, Helen I., 1906-1908 (Scrapbook 280.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Thornbury, Zita L., 1904-1907 (Scrapbook 282 (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Van Cleef, Eugenia, 1904-1908 (Scrapbook 283.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1908 — Wright, Margaret C., 1904-1906 (Scrapbook 156)
  - VC 1909 — Brown, Beatrice (Daw), 1903-1911 (Scrapbook 157)
  - VC 1909 — Carpenter, Hazel (Leach), 1905-1915 (Scrapbook 158)
  - VC 1909 — Hasbrouck, Elsa, 1905-1909 (Scrapbook 286 (Oversize))
  - VC 1909 — Miller, Nellie I., 1905-1909 (Scrapbook 159)
  - VC 1909 — Searles, Marjorie (Squier), 1905-1909 (Scrapbook 287 (Oversize))
  - VC 1909 — Woodruff, Edith S., 1905-1909 (Scrapbook 160)
  - VC 1910 — Blegen, Elizabeth (Pierce), 1906-1910 (Scrapbook 161)
  - VC 1910 — Damon, Gladys L., undated (Scrapbook 163)
  - VC 1910 — Jacobs, Lucile Chace, undated (Scrapbook 164)
  - VC 1910 — La Roche, Mary L., undated (Scrapbook 165)
  - VC 1910 — Purdie, Alice May (Dike), 1906-1910 (Scrapbook 166)
  - VC 1910 — Thom, Katharine (Bissell), 1907-1910 (Scrapbook 167)
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford), 1907-1909 (Scrapbook 288.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1911 — Hamilton, Dorothy (Crawford), 1909-1911 (Scrapbook 288.b (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1911 — Lowell, Gladys M. (Ballou), 1907-1908 (Scrapbook 238 (Oversize))
  - VC 1911 — McDonnell, Irene (Palmer), 1910-1912 (Scrapbook 168)
  - VC 1911 — Perry, Alice Maida, 1907-1911 (Scrapbook 169)
  - VC 1911 — Tag, Florence K., 1907-1911 (Scrapbook 290 (Oversize))
  - VC 1912 — Haessler, Mildred (Barnes), 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 248 (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1912 — Bigelow, Dorothy, 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 291 (Oversize))
  - VC 1912 — Brown, Edith Crosby, 1908-1910 (Scrapbook 170)
  - VC 1912 — Brown, Edith Crosby, 1908-1910 (Scrapbook 171)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart), 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 172)
  - VC 1912 — Clary, Marjorie (Stewart), 1908-1915 (Scrapbook 292 (Oversize))
  - VC 1912 — James, Helen C., 1908-1914 (Scrapbook 278 (Oversize))
  - VC 1912 — Large, Helen B., 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 173)
  - VC 1912 — Maas, Edith, undated (Scrapbook 174)
  - VC 1912 — Maas, Edith, undated (Scrapbook 175)
  - VC 1912 — Tibbets, Helen (Ferris), 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 228 (Oversize))
  - VC 1912 — Wesbrook, Elizabeth (Barney), 1908-1912 (Scrapbook 176)
  - VC 1913 — Casselman, Margery (Davenport), 1904-1913 (Scrapbook 177)
  - VC 1913 — Dayton, Elinor (Buss), 1909-1915 (Scrapbook 296 (Oversize))
  - VC 1913 — Gerrity, Margaret (McKee), undated (Scrapbook 230 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French), 1910-1912 (Scrapbook 178)
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French), 1911-1912 (Scrapbook 299.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French), 1912-1913 (Scrapbook 299.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Babbott, Elizabeth (French), 1913-1914 (Scrapbook 299.c (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Buckingham, Mary, 1911-1914 (Scrapbook 179)
  - VC 1914 — Eldridge, Muriel (Tilden), 1910-1918 (Scrapbook 302 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Glenn, Vanessa (Glucksmann), 1910-1912 (Scrapbook 304 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — McGuire, Frances (Grant), 1910-1927 (Scrapbook 243 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Morgan, Jane (Mayo), 1910-1921 (Scrapbook 303 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Smith, Charlotte Rindge (Peet), 1910-1914 (Scrapbook 305 (Oversize))
  - VC 1914 — Thayer, Gretchen, 1911-1914 (Scrapbook 180)
  - VC 1914 — Whitman, Dorothy, 1912-1914 (Scrapbook 306 (Oversize))
  - VC 1915 — Denison, Miriam (Ellinwood), 1911-1915 (Scrapbook 307 (Oversize))
  - VC 1915 — Finn, Mona (Cowell), 1911-1916 (Scrapbook 308 (Oversize))
  - VC 1915 — Milham, Alma (Hass), 1911-1915 (Scrapbook 181)
  - VC 1915 — Sherwin, Martha May (Reynolds), 1911-1913 (Scrapbook 309.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1915 — Strayer, Maude Louise, 1911-1915 (Scrapbook 309.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1915 — Strayer, Maude Louise, 1915-1924 (Scrapbook 182)
  - VC 1916 — Allen, Mildred, undated (Scrapbook 313 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Dix, Bertha (Pringle), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 312 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Fritz, Esther (Jones), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 326 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Hale, Evelyn Wickham, undated (Scrapbook 310 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Hopson, Lucile, 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 295 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Jones, Janet (Ullrich), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 311 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Tatnall, Helen (Shaw), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 183)
  - VC 1916 — Tatnall, Helen (Shaw), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 315 (Oversize))
  - VC 1916 — Yocum, Helen (Woodbury), 1912-1916 (Scrapbook 322 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Blood-Smyth, Gertrude (Haff), 1913-1917 (Scrapbook 320 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Diamond, Elizabeth (Stafford), 1913-1917 (Scrapbook 317 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Glover, Frances G. (Cheney), circa 1913-1915 (Scrapbook 319 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Goodrich, Anne (Swann), 1913-1917 (Scrapbook 184)
  - VC 1917 — Jenison, Monell, 1914-1917 (Scrapbook 316 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Miller, Lilian May, undated (Scrapbook 185)
  - VC 1917 — Miller, Lilian May, undated (Scrapbook 186)
  - VC 1917 — Otis, Jeannette (Miller), 1913-1917 (Scrapbook 318 (Oversize))
  - VC 1917 — Tibbals, Bertha (Hasler), 1914-1915 (Scrapbook 187)
  - VC 1917 — Tibbals, Bertha (Hasler), 1915-1916 (Scrapbook 188)
  - VC 1918 — Bartow, Virginia, 1914-1922 (Scrapbook 321 (Oversize))
  - VC 1918 — Genzmer, Margaret (Edge), 1914-1917 (Scrapbook 323 (Oversize))
  - VC 1918 — Mann, Isabel R., 1914-1918 (Scrapbook 189)
  - VC 1918 — Mason, Mary, 1914-1918 (Scrapbook 190)
  - VC 1918 — Simmons, Hilda (Gemmer), undated (Scrapbook 191)
  - VC 1918 — Watson, Mary Abell, undated (Scrapbook 325 (Oversize))
  - VC 1918 — Zimmerman, Marie-Luise (Binder), 1914-1918 (Scrapbook 324 (Oversize))
  - VC 1919 — Chickering, Katharine, 1915-1919 (Scrapbook 192)
  - VC 1919 — Gindele, Josephine (Clarkson), 1915 (Scrapbook 224 (Oversize))
  - VC 1919 — Hansen, Alice E. (McBride), 1913-1921 (Scrapbook 327 (Oversize))
  - VC 1919 — Moxley, Marian (Wightman), 1915-1919 (Scrapbook 331 (Oversize))
  - VC 1919 — Reeder, Barbara (Lorenz), 1915-1920 (Scrapbook 231 (Oversize))
  - VC 1919 — Watkins, Agnes, 1915-1919 (Scrapbook 333 (Oversize))
  - VC 1920 — Benedict, Elizabeth (Emerson), 1918-1920 (Scrapbook 194)
  - VC 1920 — Kunz, Ruth (Guibord) [Missing as of November 2022], undated (Scrapbook 195)
  - VC 1920 — Van de Visse, Helen (Lewis), 1916-1920 (Scrapbook 334 (Oversize))
  - VC 1920 — Williams, Margaret (Plum), 1916-1920 (Scrapbook 335 (Oversize))
  - VC 1921 — Chamberlin, Gladys (Wagner), 1918-1921 (Scrapbook 336 (Oversize))
  - VC 1921 — Kinley, Harriet, 1917-1920 (Scrapbook 337 (Oversize))
  - VC 1921 — McGregor, Catherine Scott, 1917-1919 (Scrapbook 338 (Oversize))
  - VC 1921 — McGregor, Catherine Scott, 1919-1921 (Scrapbook 339 (Oversize))
  - VC 1921 — McKelden, Sarah A. (Bennet), 1910-1971 (Scrapbook 216 (Oversize))
  - VC Ex 1922 — Billings, Katharine H., 1918-1922 (Scrapbook 340 (Oversize))
  - VC 1922 — Carroll, Ruth (Robinson), 1918-1919 (Scrapbook 196)
  - VC 1922 — Carroll, Ruth (Robinson), 1920 (Scrapbook 197)
  - VC 1922 — Carroll, Ruth (Robinson), 1921-1922 (Scrapbook 198)
  - VC 1922 — Dickinson, Eleanor (Shaler), 1920 (Scrapbook 199)
  - VC 1922 — Hussey, Miriam, 1918-1922 (Scrapbook 268 (Oversize))
  - VC 1923 — Capen, Eleanor (Marshall), 1920-1923 (Scrapbook 162)
  - VC 1923 — Pierce, Mary Florence (Bennet), 1921-1923 (Scrapbook 272 (Oversize))
  - VC 1924 — DeForest, Helen (Hart), 1920-1924 (Scrapbook 273 (Oversize))
  - VC 1924 — Janish, Jeanne (Russell) [contains VC 1896 Lucile (Cross) Russell in the same volume], 1887-1938 (Scrapbook 250 (Oversize))
  - VC 1924 — Stone, Mildred F., [1922-1924] (Scrapbook 235 (Oversize))
  - VC 1925 — Meiss, Jean S. (Hoffheimer), 1921-1925 (Scrapbook 343 (Oversize))
  - VC 1925 — Merrell, Alice Allen, 1921-1925 (Scrapbook 236 (Oversize))
  - VC 1926 — Hasbrouck, Ruth I., 1922-1926 (Scrapbook 342 (Oversize))
  - VC 1926 — Southwick, Mildred, undated (Scrapbook 328 (Oversize))
  - VC 1927 — Sims, Margaret Hitchcock (Hopkins), 1923-1925 (Scrapbook 244.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1927 — Sims, Margaret Hitchcock (Hopkins), 1925-1927 (Scrapbook 244.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1929 — Irmisch, Alice (Karslake), 1926-1927 (Scrapbook 154)
  - VC 1929 — Irmisch, Alice (Karslake), 1927-1929 (Scrapbook 155)
  - VC 1929 — McKnight, Leila, 1925 (Box 212 (Scrapbook 359))
  - VC 1929 — Scudder, Saidie E., 1925-1927 (Scrapbook 252 (Oversize))
  - VC 1929 — Scudder, Saidie E., 1927-1929 (Scrapbook 253 (Oversize))
  - VC 1929 — Wall, Louise (Baker), 1927-1929 (Scrapbook 222 (Oversize))
  - VC 1929 — Wall, Louise (Baker), 1925-1927 (Scrapbook 345 (Oversize))
  - VC 1930 — Davies, Katherine (Stringfellow), 1926-1931 (Scrapbook 241.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1930 — Davies, Katherine (Stringfellow), 1929-1930 (Scrapbook 241.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1930 — Wills, Jane (Aubrey), undated (Scrapbook 257 (Oversize))
  - VC 1931 — Yater, Ruth Millicent (Becker), 1927-1962 (Scrapbook 221)
  - VC 1932 — Wright, Elizabeth (Fish), 1928-1932 (Scrapbook 200)
  - VC 1934 — Thomas, Bertha, 1929-1935 (Scrapbook 262 (Oversize))
  - VC 1938 — Lent, Emily I., 1934-1938 (Scrapbook 193)
  - VC 1940 — Dain, Katherine, circa 1936-1940 (Scrapbook 203)
  - VC 1941 — Harrison, Susan Brookhart, 1937-1941 (Scrapbook 240.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1941 — Harrison, Susan Brookhart, 1937-1942 (Scrapbook 240.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1941 — Tucker, Ruth, 1936-1941 (Scrapbook 201)
  - VC 1941 — Tucker, Ruth, 1936-1941 (Scrapbook 202)
  - VC 1944 — Herrity, Joann (Lovdahl), 1940-1942 (Scrapbook 298.a (Oversize))
  - VC 1944 — Herrity, Joann (Lovdahl), 1943-1944 (Scrapbook 298.b (Oversize))
  - VC 1946 — Brandenberger, Roberta (Hanson), 1927-1946 (Scrapbook 254 (Oversize))
  - VC 1946 — Brandenberger, Roberta (Hanson), 1942-1946 (Scrapbook 255 (Oversize))
  - VC 1948 — Hill, Cornelia (Hassan), 1945-1948 (Scrapbook 293 (Oversize))
  - VC 1948 — Hill, Cornelia (Hassan), 1945-1948 (Scrapbook 294 (Oversize))
  - VC 1951 — Brower, Nancy (Tasman), 1947-1951 (Scrapbook 281 (Oversize))
  - VC 1956 — Ehrman, Anita L., undated (Scrapbook 275 (Oversize))
  - VC 1956 — Ehrman, Anita L., undated (Scrapbook 276 (Oversize))
  - VC 1956 — Ehrman, Anita L., undated (Scrapbook 277 (Oversize))
  - VC 1960 — Cabot, Lynne O'Berry "Terry", 1956-1957 (Scrapbook 256 (Oversize))
  - VC 1964 — Garrell, Eleanor Mae (Berger), 1960-1963 (Scrapbook 314 (Oversize))
  - "Prof. Pricilla H. Braislin (Math, 1865-1887)", 1885-1889 (Scrapbook 56)
- SERIES X. SYLLABI, 1914-1940
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Economics A and AA, "Outlines of Economics,", circa 1914 (Box 154)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Economics E, "Socialism: Outlines for Reading and Study," (Box 154)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — Economics EE, "Labor Problem: Outline for Reading and Study," (Box 154)
  - VC 1915 — Spalding, Gertrude A. — English F and FF, "Eng Lit from Beowulf to Johnson,", circa 1915 (Box 154)
  - VC 1923 — Richardson, Margaret H. (Laidlaw) — Philosophy, "Introduction to Philosophy" [see Margaret H. Laidlaw Richarson Papers ], 1918
  - VC 1940 — Deutch, Katherine (Sanford) — Art [105], 1939-1940 (Box 154)
  - VC 1960 — McInnis, Elizabeth "Lala" (LaFollette) — Religion 105, 1956 (Box 154)
  - Unidentified — Chemistry, "Topics in Chemisty and Certain Applications of Chemistry,", 1874 (Box 154)
  - Unidentified — Natural Philosophy, "Topics in Natural Philosophy, Embracing Undulations, Sound, Light and Heat,", 1874 (Box 154)
- SERIES XI. PHOTOGRAPH ALBUMS, 1865-circa 1989; [336 volumes]
  Some photograph albums are available online via the Vassar College Libraries' Digital Library.
  - VC 1865-1868 [Special] — Jones, Ella H. (Album 9)
  - VC 1866-1867 [Preparatory] — Roberts, Pamela A. (Album 10)
  - VC 1867 — Warner, Harriette A. (Album 4)
  - VC 1868 — Brooks, Anna Baker (Album 2)
  - VC 1868 — Warner, Martha S. (Album 265)
  - VC 1869 — Smith, Elisabeth Sayre (Album 7)
  - VC 1870 — Dalton, Louise (Merrett) (Album 3)
  - VC 1870 — Mineah, Mary A. (Album 1)
  - VC [1870?] — Notman, Montreal, 1869-1870 (Album 72)
  - VC 1871 — Hopper, Euphemia W. (Album 6)
  - VC 1871 — Woodbury, Mary (Nicoll), circa 1867-1871 (Album 285)
  - VC 1873 — Angell, Isabel (Album 13)
  - VC 1873 — Bell, Julia (Album 15)
  - VC 1873 — Corliss, Lucy F. (Album 29)
  - VC 1873 — Hopson, Mary A. (Album 31)
  - VC 1873 — Perry, M. Eva, undated (Album 28)
  - VC 1873 — Swift, Elma D. (Album 16)